# MailGuard Database Migration Fix

## Run these commands in Render.com Shell:

# 1. Mark existing migrations as applied (stamp current state)
flask db stamp head

# 2. Create new migration for MailGuard tables
flask db migrate -m 'Add MailGuard email intelligence tables'

# 3. Apply the new migration
flask db upgrade

# 4. Verify tables were created
python -c 'from application import create_app; from app.mailguard.models import db; app = create_app(); app.app_context().push(); print(\
MailGuard
tables:\); print([t.name for t in db.metadata.sorted_tables if \mail\ in t.name])'

